THEME SONG: In the not too
distant future, next Sunday AD,
there was a guy named Joel, not
too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic
Institute, just another face
in a red jumpsuit.
He did a good job
cleaning up the place.
But his bosses didn't like him
so they shot him into space.
We'll send him cheesy movies,
the worst we can find.
La-la-la.
He'll have to sit
and watch them all.
And we'll monitor his mind.
La-la-la.
Now, keep in mind Joel can't
control where the movies being
or end.
La-la-la.
Because he used
those special parts
to make his robot friends.
Robot Roll Call.
All right, let's go!
Cambot.
Pan Left!
Gypsy!
Hi, girl!
Tom Servo.
What a cool guy!
Crow!
He's a wisecracker.
If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes,
and other science facts.
La-la-la.
Then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show.
I should really just relax for
Mystery Science Theater 3000!
And the poor, helpless Velveteen Rabbit scurried and blurried and bustled about,
for he was frightened of the Bully-Wully-Wully-Wolfie.
Oh wow, this is so cool. Best part coming up next.
Hi everybody, I'm just reading my robot monsters here, their favorite book.
30 seconds to commercial sign.
The Bully-Wully-Wolfie-Wully-Wully-Wolfie Rabbit said, "Oh mommy, I'm so terribly, awfully, squeezy."
Oh Joel, come on, do all the voices. Come on Joel, feel it.
He said, "Oh mommy, I'm so terribly, awfully, horribly, frightened.
Whatever will become of me, I want to be warm and fuzzy and furry and cozy and squeezy."
[chatter]
[music]
And the furry, blurry, worthy, little Wuzzy-Wiffle,
chuckled, chuckled in the warm home of their brother's arm.
Oh you guys, it's the agents of hell.
Oh Joel, that was delightful. I'm thoroughly enchanted.
Now get to the invention exchange, Meryl Streep.
Jeez, oh fine. Hey, Cam-Bom, move it in a little bit.
This thing is called the mind control guitar. I based it on the premise of the Think System from that movie, The Music Man.
Of course I know about the Think System. I invented it. Robert Preston stole it from me.
Yeah, and what about Scarecrow's brain?
Yeah, well whatever, you know. I thought it'd be really neat if a person could merely think of a sound
and it could be played by this mind control guitar.
Yeah, just think of it as a real guitar to help those dopey guys who play air guitar at parties.
And of course, sir, with research, there is hope.
Yeah, now what happens is you can see in this helmet, there are sensors that read my thoughts,
the impulses travel down these lines here, and then they're played by this servo control hands,
eliminating that costly middle man, your motor skills.
So now all I have to do is think of a juicy rock riff and the guitar plays it. Check it out, watch.
Yeah, all I gotta do is add the appropriate facial grimaces,
wear spandex, and meet with the ladies after the show.
I have seen the future of rock and roll and his name is Joel Robinson.
I have seen the future of trite cliches and his name is Tom Servo.
I have seen the future of an overripe load pan and his name is Crow.
Hey, yo, you think you're so smart, I will hold that one in five years.
Is that the price or is that your telephone number?
It's a free for all!
Well, I could certainly see how that would...
Well, anyway, our invention exchange this week is similar, I admit, but different in subtle yet important ways.
I'll take this, Frank. Thank you very much.
These are squeeze toy guitars, Joel, made from discarded doggy chew toys and these are our roadies, Jerry and Sylvia.
Jerry, give me a little bit more monitor down here.
Come on, let's wham!
Wait for it, Frank.
Now every scientist worth his salt knows that doggies love chirpy little chew toys and they love rock and roll.
We've combined them both.
Come on, let's rock this mother!
Let the cowboys ride! Jerry, run the lights!
Get the camera! This is our new song, Plastic Man!
Plastic Man!
That ought to hold them, Frank.
Good night, Boudicott! Chief Trix says good night! Good night, everybody!
Now your experiment this week, Joel, features a giant, blotated mutant lizard.
Meatloaf?
Godzilla!
Yes, quite. And it features a giant lobster and a tanker full of drawn butter.
It was a rock lobster!
Big finish, Frank! Big finish! Big finish!
Big finish!
Oh, no!
Whoa!
Come on!
You're gonna get it, aren't you?
You little monster!
(MUSIC)
(LAUGHTER)
Comedy Central.